Hanste ji, we, Director sahab, will
present to you a very long term
chart. The results of Bajaj Auto have come out,
or let me tell you, you will see Harsh and ji, good
morning ji, the
money has flown in. In fact, the numbers, if you pay
attention, have
seen a slightly better performance than expected, but there was
pressure on margins and there was a factory, the way
Rome saw an increase in additional force,
in the last quarter, there will be
muscle, but where are they performing, if you look at the
revenue front,
you will see an increase of up to one percent, the
company has vested a revenue of over 9000 crores, the
estimate was 8948 crores,
this is definitely a tree of vitamin capacity,
see, it is better than expected, the
son of 1372 crores, the mother was assuming that the
son would be around 1200-80 crores,
along with that, you will
see the profitability figure has come above 12 crores,
where the estimate was around 1100-60
crores, there is pressure son, and
in profit, along with the matchstick, and if
you pay attention to the matchstick, then this cream  It has come to 15.27 and
this time it is 19.4
in the matchstick two-wheeler market. Although the
market of the company has been seen improving a little for the third time,
but it is
clear that such an increase was seen in the raw material cost, due to
which there was a
rise in the prices of material and plastic,
its effect was seen in the third quarter on the
matchstick
that when Shekhar Yadav had pressed the maximum on the button, the
revenue of
matches seems to be difficult, now see whether the market is
liking the fast base, this is the biggest
question for this time,
subscribe for the
war,
but here another
subscribe
and a
smooth was given, now
after these results, where you are
thinking about
how you will complete the 3436 effect,
I will look towards buying a lot,
its link is that if you look at the daily chart,
there you will see for the height of side Adams,
in three days a correction was seen,
condom, similarly, not
grinding down stock, so that wholesaler of partition
baby, we find the pattern positive,
so my question is that this  Bar entries will give
your friends just 28. Now
according to me, you should buy on that
demo. The average is 3370, so
below 3370 you have to chant 31st, but
stop the target Chhattisgarh
that 1136 reputation was done. You
come from the country defined Chaupar, by committing a murder,
children subscribe to the percentage
that a good, later, there are many companies in the next,
crimes against them will be under watch
because we started with Bajaj Auto, the
seat should also be under watch. Aircraft
Masala is bad, so this counter in the seat category,
you can see here, the
figure of 16 crores has increased from 157 to 2004,
Vitamin 58 has declined.
Operating margin, while being around
five, has
come to around the city. We have also seen a lot of pressure in Cross Matches
and a net consolidated loss has been
posted by the company of around 22 crores,
so the performance has been very poor, shades were used. On the
other hand, L&T Infotech numbers 66 Very
strong number one company has posted,
revenue growth is around 6%
Three Smith 6.7 per cent Gaurav Rose Company will
present constant factor C basis also
growth of 9.2% has been seen,
margin of 17.97 per cent Hanuman 7.5 per cent from
and this is big,
profitability has come at 17.27 for Innocent,
around 11 plants have
seen an increase, so that is Electronics
WhatsApp L&T Infotech's left, but pay
attention to the second quarter results, high and
ward performance will be seen a little bit,
you will see it in use, and
in the back category, the dross
premium UK is up by only 6 per
cent, a figure of 4700 87 crores was
seen, profitability has
declined by up to 29 per cent Introduction
Loss has been seen in the health insurance segment
and
if you pay attention on a very simple quarter-on-quarter basis, it has been
seen increasing, a
lot of stagnation was seen in motor insurance
People are firm despite Dawood. Currently,
ICICI Lombard had a
weak quarter by taking the fifth quarter. Profit has
declined by up to 7 percent.
Figure of 95 crores. Prabhu flat relief. Now a slight
increase.
4184. Travel on the road or see on Twitter.
Cent has been removed from 48 and matches have also come down from
50% to just 25 heads.
Teracom's son Tejaswi Network
also had a weak quarter.
Due to the problem in the keypad, there has been some slowdown in custom payments and new orders. This is
a reflection of the same. This quarterly loss is around
25 crores to 24 crores.
Here you see,
at the arrest level also, the only company posted a loss
of crores and revenue has declined by about 30 percent. On the
other hand, Singh Gill had a
slow quarter. If you compare it with God, the
revenue is only 10 years old.
Crossing the figure of 641 crores, the
margin is coming down to 2 to 4 crores.
Matches are improving slightly but
profit is 31  Even now it has increased from just two crores to
102 crores and a figure of half a crore
or you should pay attention to Speechless India, the
result has increased by ten percent in Ashlaghya,
growth of up to three times has been seen in Beta, operating margin is
around stem cell, this tempered glass
half, nothing has changed, ticket profit family has
seen a slight dip, a
decline of three percent, profit has increased by
nine and a half percent in domestic share,
exports have seen an increase of up to 1965,
so the quarterly results of Raees are
good,
let's have some discussions here
on these stocks where